rtsoft.com 2019-12-16

# Robinson Technologies - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY NOTICE  
Effective Date: May 25, 2018  
(Last Updated: May 25, 2018)**

We respect the privacy rights of our customers and protect the personal information collected, stored and used in connection with our products, services and websites. Your privacy is important to us. To further this commitment, we have adopted this privacy policy notice ("Privacy Policy Notice" or "Privacy Policy") to guide you on how we collect, store, and use the information you may provide to us.?Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

Table of Contents  

1\. Protecting Your Privacy

2\. What Information Do We Collect?

3\. How Do We Use Your Information?

4\. Who Do We Share Your Information With?

5\. Is Your Information Secure?

6\. Does Your Information Go Across Borders?

7\. Is Sensitive Information Collected?

8\. What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Collection, Use, and Distribution of Your Personal Information?

9\. Children's Privacy

10\. California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

11\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

12\. Contacting Us

_1\. Protecting Your Privacy_

Robinson Technologies Corporation (referred to as "we" or "us") provide interactive software products ("Game") via online services such as Apple App Store and Google Play Store. We own and operate www.rtsoft.com (our "Site") to provide access to information about us, the Game, forums, or provide technical support to our customers (our "Content"). 

We are committed to protecting the privacy of all people who interface with our Game and our Site. This Privacy Policy Notice outlines how we intend to collect, use and manage the protection of your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy Notice, and contact us if you have any questions. By registering or accessing this Site and/or our Game, you agree that we may collect, use and process your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy Notice. BY ACCESSING THIS SITE AND/OR USING THE GAME, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND AND ACCEPT THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU AGREE AND UNDERSTAND THAT YOU ARE BOUND BY ALL TERMS, POLICIES AND GUIDELINES INCORPORATED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE AND/OR THE GAME. 

Back to top

_2\. What Information Do We Collect?_

Personal information is information that identifies you and that may be used to contact you online or offline. We may collect personal information from you automatically and on a voluntary basis, as described below. Our primary goals in collecting and using information are to create your account, provide services to you, improve our services, contact you, conduct research and create reports for internal use.? 

Our Site

While you are browsing our Site, we collect personal information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address automatically. Your IP address is included in a log file containing non-personal information such as your computer's operating system, access times, browser type and coarse geo-location. We may use this information to monitor and analyze your use of the services. In addition, we may ask you to submit and we may process data that is personal to you, including but not limited to your name, user name and email address. We may use this information to create a user profile. We may use your email address to contact you about our password reset. 

Forums

We may offer you the ability to post content to a blog, message board, chat room or within our applications or other forums ("Forums"). In order to use the Forums, you must allow us to collect a user name and email address from you. Additionally, you may optionally provide a profile picture, your location and user names for instant messaging services (e.g. AIM, Skype, etc.). You may also choose to sign up with your Facebook account. If so, then we may collect your first and last name, your profile picture and other information made publicly available by you, as well as the email address associated with your account. This personal information may be combined with non-personal information you provide, such as your date of birth, interests, occupation and any other information you choose to contribute about yourself. 

You should be aware that any visitor to the Forums may read your postings on the Forums. Furthermore, any information that you may post to a Forum, including your username or other account profile information, will be disclosed and available to all users and viewers of that Forum, and therefore, will be no longer private. We cannot guarantee the security of such information that is disclosed or communicated online in public areas such as the Forums, and you provide such information at your own risk. We do not author, edit or endorse any Forum. You acknowledge and agree that we have no responsibility for the accuracy or availability of information provided on any Forum. We reserve the right at any time, in our sole discretion, to remove any content that a user may post on any Forum and restrict user access to any Forum. 

Social Media Interaction

You also can engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter (or third-party social media plug-ins and applications). When you engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the 'likes' you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with our content. 

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our Sites (and/or applications), and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. When you provide personal information to us through an application, on our Sites, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties. 

Through some social networking sites' privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use. 

Customer Service

We may collect information that you provide to us, such as your name, email address and/or telephone calls with names and numbers to return calls when you contact our customer support and we may use that information to contact you about your gaming experience with our Game. 

Game Data Collection

Whenever you play our Game, we collect data about all of your interactions with the Game and with the other players inside the Game via server log files and/or leaderboards. We use this information to help improve your game experience and monitor the performance of the game. Please note that our third party service providers, later described, may have access to information such as your device identifier ("device ID"), advertising identifier ("ad ID"), MAC address, IMEI, locale (specific location where a given language is spoken), geo-location information, and IP address. In order for Tapjoy to function on older Android devices which do not have an ad ID, telephone number may be collected in order to create a unique ID. 

Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that we transfer to your computer and/or device, to identify a user's computer/device and to "remember" things about your visit, such as your preferences or a user name and password. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of our service, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although by doing so, you may not be able to access or use all of the features of the service. 

Advertising

From time to time, you may see our Game advertised in other services. After clicking on one of these advertisements and installing our Game, you will become a user of our Game. In order to verify the installs, a device ID may be shared with the advertiser. 

We may feature advertisements served by third parties that deliver cookies to your computer/device so the Content you access and advertisements you see can be tracked. Since the third party advertising companies associate your computer/device with a number, they will be able to recognize your computer/device each time they send you an advertisement. These advertisers may use information about your visits to our Site and third party sites and applications in order to measure advertisement performance and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the data collection practices of these third party advertisers, and we encourage you to check their privacy policies to learn more about their use of cookies and other technology. 

Back to top

_3\. How Do We Use Your Information?_

We use information collected through our Site for purposes described in this Privacy Policy or disclosed to you in connection with our Site. For example, we may use your information to:  
Create game accounts and allow users to play our Game;  
Operate and improve our Site;  
Understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our Site;  
Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;  
Send you related information, including confirmations, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages.  

It is our responsibility to keep accurate, complete and up-to-date records, so any changes you make in the Game regarding your personally identifiable information will go into effect as quickly as technically possible. We reserve the right to retain the non-personally identifiable data collected during your use of the Site or Game. 

We also reserve the right to delete messages, User Content and accounts in whole or in part, at our discretion, that we find offensive to the general public, uses profanity, causes complaints from other users, is not suitable for a general audience or infringes the intellectual property rights of any third party. For example, talk of drugs, alcohol, violence, strong language, gambling, crude humor, sexual themes or is suggestive in nature is prohibited. 

Finally, we keep your personal information only as long as we need it for the purposes for which we collected it, or as permitted or required by applicable law. 

Back to top

_4\. Who Do We Share Your Information With?_

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party. We do engage in the following activities:

We share statistics of each user's activities and data within reports that are used internally to analyze the Game, its features and performance.  
We may release your information as permitted by law or when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our rights; or protect the rights, property, or safety of use or our uses or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.  
We may share your information in connection with any merger, sale of our assets, or financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.  
We may share information about you with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

Third Party Services

Our services may contain third party tracking tools from our service providers, examples of which include tracking tools from Google on our Site. Such third parties may use cookies (which may contain your IP address) and other software tools in our services to enable them to collect and analyze user information on our behalf. A non-exhaustive list of the names of these third party service providers, along with their opt-out choices, is provided below. 

Our Site

On our Site, we analyze statistical data using third party service, Google Analytics. To learn more about the Google Analytics cookie, including how to opt out, please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

If you access our Site via a mobile device, please note that Google may also share your information with its advertising service providers, DoubleClick and AdMob. Please review Google's privacy policy at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/> to learn more. 

Please note that if you are logged into a Facebook and/or Twitter account, those social networking sites may collect information about your online activity as well. For more information, please consult their privacy policies. 

Our Game

We may use Tapjoy (Ads) and a restricted version of Flurry (Analytics) for our Game. You can learn more about Tapjoy, including how to opt out, by visiting <https://home.tapjoy.com/info/about-tapjoy/privacy-policy/>. You may also choose not to watch the ads served in-app by Tapjoy and/or control your ad settings through your device. You can learn more about Flurry, including how to opt out, by visiting <http://www.flurry.com/privacy-policy.html>. 

We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to our Site or Game, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information. 

Back to top

_5\. Is Your Information Secure?_

The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect guest information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. In the event of a data breach involving our users' unencrypted personal information, you will be notified via email and/or notice on the affected Site or Game. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. 

Back to top

_6\. Does Your Information Go Across Borders?_

We use third party servers in the United States to host our Site and Game and to store information and archives. By visiting our Site and by downloading or using our Game, you consent to having your personal and non-personal information and user activity data transferred and processed as described herein. 

Back to top

_7\. Is Sensitive Information Collected?_

We do not require you to provide any "sensitive information" as a requirement to use our Site or any of our Game. "Sensitive Information" means any personal information related to health, race, ethnicity, political views, religion, professional status, philosophical view, and trade or union affiliation. Sensitive Information that you disclose to "everyone" on a discussion forum or through a social networking site in connection with our Site or Game may be collected and held by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy Notice. We do not use or share Sensitive Information with third parties. Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns about any Sensitive Information that you may have disclosed to us or to other users during your use of our Site or Game that we may have collected. We do collect non-personally identifiable information regarding Site and Game usage, including but not limited to the top country, city and language by aggregate usage as provided by the social networking site. 

Back to top

_8\. What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Collection, Use, and Distribution of Your Personal Information?_

You have the right to see what personally identifiable information we hold about you if you request it.

You also have the right to be forgotten and your data removed upon request in applicable cases.

In order to place a request, please contact us using our information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Back to top

_9\. Children's Privacy_

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. We encourage parents to spend time online with their children and urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, email addresses or phone numbers without parental permission when using the Internet. If you believe that we have unintentionally collected information on your child under the age of 13 via our Site or Game, we ask that you contact us so that we can delete that information. Please email us at support@rtsoft.com or via our physical details below. 

Back to top

_10\. California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights_

Under the laws of the State of California, California Residents who have an established business relationship with us may choose to opt out of our disclosure of personal information about them to third parties for direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, our policy is not to disclose personal information collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval, email [support@rtsoft.com](mailto:support@rtsoft.com). 

Do Not Track Signals

In September 2013, California enacted amendments to the California Online Privacy Protection Act (California Business & Professions Code §§22575-22579) which require operators of websites to disclose how they respond to "do not track" (DNT) signals from browsers used by consumers or other mechanisms that provide consumers a choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about the consumer's online activities over time and across different websites or online services. While some newer browsers have incorporated "Do Not Track" features which, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the web sites you visit indicating that you do not wish your online activity to be tracked, a DNT protocol that can be implemented across multiple devices and sites has not yet been widely adopted. Currently, our computer system does not support, and cannot act on DNT signal headers that we may receive; accordingly, the choices that we provide you concerning our collection and use of personally identifiable information will continue to operate as described in this policy. 

For Minors

California residents under the age of 18 have the right to remove, or request the removal of, content or information they have posted to the Forums. This request can be made by emailing us at [support@rtsoft.com](mailto:support@rtsoft.com). Please again be advised that any information posted to the Forums is publicly viewable. We strongly recommend that all users avoid posting personal or sensitive information at any time. 

Please note that residual copies of User Content and/or information that have been deleted may remain on our backup servers. We are not required to remove posted User Content or information if it has been rendered anonymous or if we are required by law to retain it. Additionally, we do not have control over third parties (e.g., other users) who may have copied or reposted the User Content or information. 

Back to top

_11\. Changes to the Privacy Policy_

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the date at the top of the page. The changes will be effective when posted. We will post a notice on [http://www.rtsoft.com](http://www.rtsoft.com/) and/or contact you if material changes have been made to the way we handle your personal information. Please check this page on a regular basis so that you remain aware of what information we collect and how we use it. 

Back to top

_12\. Contacting Us_

For enquiries regarding this Privacy Policy Notice and personal information, please contact:

By Email: [support@rtsoft.com](mailto:support@rtsoft.com). 

By Mail:

Robinson Technologies  
P.0. Box 101  
FUKUYAMA POST OFFICE  
FUKUYAMA CITY, HIROSHIMA 720-8799
